[{"answer": "Well, you know, Piers, it's pretty -- it's pretty exciting and to think that I'm sharing with you, that's even more exciting.", "docId": "120321pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "How you are feeling about that?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "He's been -- he's been very kind.", "docId": "120321pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "Has he been generous?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "OMNEY: He's watching.", "docId": "120321pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "Will he be watching this interview?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "Hi, sweetheart.", "docId": "120321pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "Is there anything you'd like to say to your husband on this special occasion?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "I am talking -- yes, not to you, Piers.", "docId": "120321pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "You are talking to Mitt, right?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "He's a much more senior person.", "docId": "120321pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "Both 16 at the time?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Actually I was -- right.", "docId": "120321pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "And you've sort of fallen for each other?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "Well, to begin with, I don't accept the premise.", "docId": "120321pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "What do you think the public aren't seeing about your husband that they should be seeing?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "You know, I think sometimes -- you know, what happened -- I will tell you, Piers, what happened to me last time, four years ago, is the misrepresentations about records and different things like that where they make you feel as though you're not being honest or you're not true to yourself which could not be further from the truth.", "docId": "120321pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "What has been the most offended you felt as his wife on the campaign so far?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "Well, you know, again, I really meant what I said last night because I have been in every -- practically every state of this nation and I've been speaking to hundreds of people every single day and seeing people.", "docId": "120321pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "What do you think about the way that debate has been framed?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "You know, this is the distractions -- this is exactly what happens in a campaign.", "docId": "120321pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "Are you having words with Mitt's senior aides about their little gaffe today?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "I laughed.", "docId": "120321pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "What was your view of that?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "Well, I think the backdrop of our meeting today is that Starbucks had record revenues and the stock price hit the highest level in its history today.", "docId": "120321pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "What kind of reaction do you expect from your shareholders?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Well, I think there is a lot of rhetoric right now because of how fierce this competition has been.", "docId": "120321pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Do they understand the problem and the solution?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "I think that's an interesting question.", "docId": "120321pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "And how much actually comes down to individual bosses of companies like yourself to take initiatives that spur the economy forward?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "If I had to one, it's not one that is very sexy, patience.", "docId": "120321pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "What is your ultimate superpower that you choose?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "I go for the original choice.", "docId": "120321pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "Who is the closest hero that has that power?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "I don't know, but --", "docId": "120321pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "What about the rights of the guy he's killed?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "You're a parent.", "docId": "120321pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "What about Trayvon Martin's rights?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "Probably, of course.", "docId": "120321pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "Would it be different if this was a black shooter and a young white boy who had been killed?", "qSentId": 493}]